<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>

<rss version="2.0" 
   xmlns:rdf="http://www.w3.org/1999/02/22-rdf-syntax-ns#"
   xmlns:admin="http://webns.net/mvcb/"
   xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
   xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
   xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
   xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
   >
<channel>
    
    <title>IAREGAMER FAQ</title>
    <link>https://iaregamer.com</link>
    <description></description>
    <dc:language>en</dc:language>
    <generator>Serendipity 2.0.4 - http://www.s9y.org/</generator>
    <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jun 2020 20:10:54 GMT</pubDate>

    <image>
    <url></url>
    <title>RSS: IAREGAMER FAQ - </title>
    <link>https://iaregamer.com</link>
    <width>100</width>
    <height>21</height>
</image>

<item>
    <title>What if I need help with my server?</title>
    <category>General</category>
    
    <content:encoded>
    (1) if your server is not responding, submit a ticket or contact us on Discord 
    (2) if you need help with scripting, contact us on Discord and let us know what you need 
    (3) confused? contact us on Discord

    </content:encoded>
    
</item>

<item>
    <title>What is the Query Port (or other port) for my server</title>
   <category>General</category>
    
    <content:encoded>
    Each game has its own category with specific information about that game including the query (and other) ports. 
	Look in the FAQ category for your game.
	If your game is not listed, or the query port is not specified then its probably the SAME as your SERVER PORT. If it still doesnt work, submit a ticket and we will find out ASAP for you (and update the FAQ)
	
 
    </content:encoded>
    
</item>

<item>
    <title>What are subusers and groups? How do I add them?</title>
   <category>Panel</category>
    
    <content:encoded>
    &lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/g45JbifloFQ&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
 
    </content:encoded>
    
</item>

<item>
    <title>My server won't start. Error: &quot;Failed to start the remote server. Error code: -1&quot; or &quot;Failed with server query&quot;</title>
   <category>Error Messages</category>
    
    <content:encoded>
Often the message (Failed with Server Query) means its just taking a long time for the server to start, give it some time and see what happens. 
Check your logs for error messages.
Your server MAY have been misconfigured and is not starting correctly.
BUT have you recently changed any files?
The most common reason is the server is crashing or fails to start because of invalid, missing files
or something is misconfigured.  
Restore the BACKUP you made before editing your server. (You DID backup, right?)
If you have NOT made any changes, contact support and we will investigate. 
    </content:encoded>
    
</item>
 <item>
    <title>What is my Query or Rcon port?</title>
   <category>Ark</category>
    
    <content:encoded>
    Query port is your SERVER port +2 
	
    </content:encoded>
 </item>
  <item>
    <title>What is my Query or Rcon port?</title>
   <category>Arma</category>
    
    <content:encoded>
    Query port is your SERVER port +1 
	
    </content:encoded>
 </item>
 
<item>
    <title>What is my Query or Rcon port?</title>
   <category>Conan Exiles</category>
    
    <content:encoded>
    Query port is your SERVER port +2 
	Rcon port is your SERVER port + 3
    </content:encoded>
 </item>
 
<item>
    <title>What is my Query port?</title>
   <category>Dayz</category>
    
    <content:encoded>
    Dayz MOD query port is your SERVER port +1 
	Dayz STANDALONE query port is your SERVER port +3 
    </content:encoded>
    
</item>
   <item>
    <title>What is my Query or Rcon port?</title>
   <category>Killing Floor</category>
    
    <content:encoded>
    Query port is your SERVER port +1 
	
    </content:encoded>
 </item>

<item>
    <title>I get an ERROR when trying to connect to the FTP using my client</title>
   <category>Panel</category>

    <content:encoded>
    Does the error mention TLS or secure connection?  Try different encryption settings. Our FTP servers do not have TLS enabled.
    </content:encoded>

</item>
<item>
    <title>How can I backup and restore my Gameserver database?</title>
            <category>Panel</category>
    
    <content:encoded>
In your Game Monitor, click on the MYSQL button and then login to PHPMYADMIN.  
Select EXPORT and save the file on your local PC.  
To RESTORE, delete ALL TABLES, FUNCTIONS and DATA from your DB then IMPORT your file 
    </content:encoded>
   
</item>

<item>
    <title>Why can't I delete some files in my game server folder?</title>
           <category>Panel</category>
    
    <content:encoded>
    We protect the &lt;strong&gt;server executable&lt;/strong&gt; and the &lt;strong&gt;startup script&lt;/strong&gt; to disallow modifications by the user.
If you need to change this file, contact support.

 
    </content:encoded>

    
</item>
<item>
    <title>How do I  validate my files  with Steam?</title>
     <category>Panel</category>
    
    <content:encoded>
 If you click on the INSTALL/UPDATE button it will validate all your Steam files.  If you want to WIPE your server and reinstall fresh, 'check' the checkbox on the upper left of the 
FILE MANAGER and REMOVE all files.  Then press INSTALL/UPDATE and Steam will replace all the missing files. 
    </content:encoded>
</item>


<item>
    <title>How do I restart my server?</title>
     <category>Dayz</category>

    <content:encoded>
BEC is preinstalled with your server. You can set the scheduler.xml to restart at intervals.
There is a scheduler_faq.xml file inside your bec/config folder that will explain in detail 
how to configure the scheduler.
As always, if you need help just ask on Discord.
    </content:encoded>
</item>

</channel>
</rss>

