<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>

<rss version="2.0" 
   xmlns:rdf="http://www.w3.org/1999/02/22-rdf-syntax-ns#"
   xmlns:admin="http://webns.net/mvcb/"
   xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
   xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
   xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
   xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
   >
<channel>
    
    <title>IAREGAMER FAQ</title>
    <link>https://iaregamer.com</link>
    <description></description>
    <dc:language>en</dc:language>
    <generator>Serendipity 2.0.4 - http://www.s9y.org/</generator>
    <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jun 2020 20:10:54 GMT</pubDate>

    <image>
    <url></url>
    <title>RSS: IAREGAMER FAQ - </title>
    <link>https://iaregamer.com</link>
    <width>100</width>
    <height>21</height>
</image>

<item>
    <title>What if I need help with my server?</title>
    <category>General</category>
    
    <content:encoded>
    (1) if your server is broken, submit a tickit or contact us on Discord 
    (2) if you need help with scripting, contact us on Discord and let us know what you need 
    (3) confused? contact us on Discord

    </content:encoded>
    
</item>

<item>
    <title>How do I contact support?</title>
    <category>General</category>
    <content:encoded>
    (1) submit a ticket on our Panel menu
    (2) join our &lt;a href=https://discord.gg/cWHAbav target=_blank &gt; Discord Server&lt;/a&gt;
    (3) Look at the LOWER RIGHT of every page: Click the Discord icon


    </content:encoded>

</item>

<item>
    <title>What is the Query Port for my server?</title>
    <category>General</category>
    
    <content:encoded>
If your gameserver is not listed below, then the QueryPort is the same as your Connection Port.
Add the number to your servers Connection port for your Query Port (or other port if available)

For Example: 
Query Port : +2
If your serverport is 7777 then your query port will be 7779

ArkSE      : QueryPort +1
Arma2      : QueryPort +1
Arma3      : QueryPort +1
DayzMod    : QueryPort +1
DayzSA     : QueryPort +3
KillingFloor : QueryPort +1
Miscreated : QueryPort +2
TheForest : QueryPort +1
UnrealTournament(all) : QueryPort +1

    </content:encoded>

    
</item>
<item>
    <title>How to Assign Game Servers to Users and Sub Users</title>
   <category>Panel</category>
    
    <content:encoded>
    &lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/NxA0O1YMZe4&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
 
    </content:encoded>
    
</item>
<item>
    <title>I have the error &quot;Failed to start the remote server. Error code: -1&quot; when starting my game server.</title>
            <category>Panel</category>
    
    <content:encoded>
Some games take a LONG time to start because they are building maps or loading lots of assets. 
Our system only waits a few seconds and then you can return to the Game Monitor. 
If the server is still starting, you will see this error code. 
Be Patient.
    </content:encoded>
    
</item>
<item>
    <title>How can I backup and restore my Gameserver database?</title>
            <category>Panel</category>
    
    <content:encoded>
In your Game Monitor, click on the MYSQL button and then login to PHPMYADMIN.  
Select EXPORT and save the file on your local PC.  
To RESTORE, delete ALL TABLES, FUNCTIONS and DATA from your DB then IMPORT your file 
    </content:encoded>
   
</item>
<item>
    <title>Why doesn't my gameserver start?</title>
    <category>Panel</category>

    <content:encoded>
Yes, there COULD be a problem with our server. BUT have you recently changed any files?
The most common reason is the server is crashing or fails to start because of invalid, missing files
or something is misconfigured.  
Restore the BACKUP you made before editing your server. (You DID backup, right?)
If you have NOT made any changes, contact support and we will investigate. 
    </content:encoded>

    
</item>
<item>
    <title>Why can't I delete some files in my game server folder?</title>
           <category>Panel</category>
    
    <content:encoded>
    We protect the &lt;strong&gt;server executable&lt;/strong&gt; and the &lt;strong&gt;startup script&lt;/strong&gt; to disallow modifications by the user.
If you need to change this file, contact support.

 
    </content:encoded>

    
</item>
<item>
    <title>How to force game server files validation with SteamCMD from Panel?</title>
     <category>Panel</category>
    
    <content:encoded>
    Delete the &lt;strong&gt;SteamApps&lt;/strong&gt; folder located in the game server root folder, then run a normal update from the Game Monitor by clicking &lt;strong&gt;Install/Update via Steam&lt;/strong&gt; button in the game server own page. You will see the file verification progress in the logging window.
 
    </content:encoded>
</item>

<item>
    <title>How do I restart my server?</title>
     <category>Dayz</category>

    <content:encoded>
BEC is preinstalled with your server. You can set the scheduler.xml to restart at intervals.
There is a scheduler_faq.xml file inside your bec/config folder that will explain in detail 
how to configure the scheduler.
As always, if you need help just ask on Discord.
    </content:encoded>
</item>

</channel>
</rss>
